Local 1199 Photograph Files 5933 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Photograph Files
1866-1992
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union
5933 P
31.75 cubic feet
31.8 linear ft.
Photographs.
The National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees 1199 News Photographs files consist of approximately 32,500 black and white photographs in 8"x10" prints; 120/220 and 35mm contact prints; and photographic negatives collected during the publication of the National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employee's periodical, known generally as 1199 News. Subjects include the early hospital strikes of the 1950s and 1960s; union activity; hospital interiors and exteriors; individuals and groups including union members and their families, political figures, celebrities, artists, and visiting dignitaries; and social, cultural, and political events sponsored or supported by Local 1199. The bulk of the photographs were taken in New York metropolitan region.
5736582
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 09, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, May 05, 2016
Biographical / Historical
Local 1199 formed in 1932 as the Pharmacists' Union of Greater New York. It affiliated with the AFL in the mid-1930s, adding Local 1199 to its name at that time; it would ultimately affiliate with the CIO in 1937 and operate under the name Retail Drug Store Employees Union, Local 1199. In those early years, the union's publication was known as the Voice of the Mortar and Pestle, the Union Pharmacist, and the Retail Drug Worker. The publication began using the name 1199 News as early as 1942. By the 1950s, its membership of pharmacists, porters, clerks and other drug store employees had grown to 6,000 workers employed throughout the New York metropolitan area in independent and chain drugstores.
In 1958 the largely white, male and Jewish drug store union leadership made common cause with predominantly female, Black and Hispanic non-professional health care employees, working to organize the staff of Montefiore Hospital in New York City. Encouraged by the successful result of this effort, the union began a massive campaign to organize workers including nurses' aides, dietary aides, orderlies, dishwashers, porters and laundry workers in all the voluntary (private and non-profit) hospitals in the New York metropolitan area. Among these nonprofessional and paraprofessional workers, 85% were African-American or Hispanic.
In May 1959, workers in seven voluntary New York metropolitan area hospitals (Mt. Sinai, Brooklyn Jewish, Lenox Hill, Beth Israel, Beth David, Flower Fifth Avenue and Bronx Hospitals) voted overwhelmingly to strike. The unprecedented and bitterly-fought strike lasted forty-six days. The accord reached by the negotiating team and the hospital administration that ended the strike resulted in a Permanent Administrative Committee Agreement which gave the workers much of what they were seeking but barred Local 1199 from resolving disputes directly with hospital management. Despite terms that effectively kept the union from representing the hospital workers, the agreement was approved.
Beginning with this proto-union for hospital employees, 1199 produced two parallel publications, the 1199 Drug News and the 1199 Hospital News (sometimes called the Local 1199 Hospital News), reflecting the two major branches that Local 1199 represented or hoped to represent.
In 1962, workers struck at Beth Israel and Manhattan Eye and Ear Hospitals, demanding formal union recognition and higher wages. The union was supported in this effort by the Committee for Justice to Hospital Workers, a group formed by Moe Foner and consisting of 100 African-American and Hispanic civic and religious leaders including Joseph Monserrat and Judge Emilio Nunez. When walkouts in eleven additional hospitals were threatened, Governor Nelson Rockefeller intervened, promising to put through legislation granting collective bargaining recognition to workers in New York City voluntary hospitals providing the union called off both the strike and threatened walkouts. The union agreed. In May 1963, Governor Rockefeller signed a bill guaranteeing hospital workers in New York City the right to unionize. In 1965 the legislature extended the bill to cover the entire state. In 1966, the 1199 Drug News and the 1199 Hospital News merged exactly at the moment that the hospital wing had gained widespread recognition. In 1970 after the union had expanded into nursing homes the publication was once again called the 1199 News.
Throughout the period of these photographs, the union was led by Leon Davis (president of Local 1199). His administration guided the union's political and social activities. African-American and Hispanic union members played an ever-growing role in the unions' struggles and achievements. Names that appear frequently in these records include representative Ramon P. Gonzalez; Hilda Joquin, a rank and file leader during the 1959 strikes who went on to become a steward and locus of support when she was fired on in 1962; Lorenzo Santiago; Ramon Malave, Secretary/Treasurer; Edward Ayash; and Gloria Arana. By 1964, Armando Ramirez, who had been an active member since the early strikes, was vice president of Local 1199 and that same year became chairman of the newly formed Spanish Affairs Committee.
Since up to 90% of the nonprofessional workers in New York City voluntary hospitals were African- American and Hispanic, Local 1199 positioned itself firmly within the civil rights movement and worked to instill a spirit of "brotherhood" at both official and social union gatherings. In 1961, Local 1199 helped Harry Van Arsdale and a fifteen person committee within the New York City Central Labor Council to form the Brotherhood Party, an independent political party for labor organized in part to combat the "exploitation, particularly of Negroes and Puerto Ricans [which] is rampant and brutal." The union supported the anti-Vietnam War/peace movement and the United Farm Workers boycotts in the mid-1970s as well. In 1964, a Comit para Asuntos Hispanos (Spanish Affairs Committee) was formed to promote involvement by Spanish-speaking members in the Administrative and everyday life of Local 1199.
In 1973, 1199 locals from several states founded the National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, RWDSU, AFL-CIO. Merger talks began with the Service Employees International Union (SEIU) in 1989, and after several false starts, District 1199(NY) joined SEIU in 1998 to become the National Health and Human Service Employees Union. At this time, 1199 News became known as 1199 SEIU News. In 2005, the publication was renamed Our Life and Times.
Scope and Contents
The 1199 News Photographs collection consists of approximately 32,500 black and white photographs in 8" x 10" prints in addition to negative film and contact prints collected during the publication of the National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employee's periodical. The images depict union activity; hospital interiors and exteriors; urban streetscapes; individuals and groups including union members and their families, political figures, celebrities, artists, and visiting dignitaries; and social, cultural, and political events sponsored or supported by Local 1199. The collection is particularly strong in its documentation of civil rights and union leaders including civil rights leaders Dr. Martin Luther and Coretta Scott King, Ralph Abernathy, Andrew Young, Hosea Williams, John Lewis, and Bayard Rustin; United Farm Workers (UFW) co-founders Csar Chvez and Dolores Huerta; and other activists including former Secretary of Labor Frances Perkins and various anti-apartheid activists. The bulk of the photographs were taken in the New York metropolitan region although they document important strikes, union activities, and political demonstrations throughout the country. The collection is a particularly rich source of images from the 1960s-early 1980s.
The photos in this collection reflect the racially diverse membership in Local 1199 where African-Americans, Latinos, and whites were the three most prominent groups; 85% of the Hospital Division was Black or Latino. The collection depicts Black and Latino union leaders including Ramon Malave, Ramon Ramirez, Theodore Mitchell, and Doris Turner; Hispanic and Black delegates and organizers such as Armando Ramirez, Vic Garcia, Lorenzo Santiago, Julio Pagan, Gloria Arana, Anibal Garcia, Hilda Joquin, Jessie Olsen, Joseph Brown, and Thelma Bowles; Hispanic and African-American retirees; and numerous Black and Latino union members on the job, at home, participating in union activities, or posing for portraits. Some images of Local 1199-sponsored activities reflect the special needs of a particular population group such as Spanish-language classes, Spanish members' meetings, Spanish Affairs Committee meetings, Hispanic retiree dinner-dances, Spanish dances, Latin festivals, and a Union Women Caribbean Dinner. There are also images of Spanish-language signage at strikes, on picket lines, and in news photos. In total, these images illustrate extensive participation by Hispanic and Black members in all levels of union life.
A large majority of folders and envelopes in National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees 1199 News Photographs have been succinctly labeled. These labels describe the subject of the images enclosed in each folder or envelope and the date the images were taken. A single folder or envelope can contain as many as fifty individual photographs. An attempt has been made here to list as many hospitals, individuals, and events as possible although the listings are not exhaustive. Researchers should consult the repository's index and the negative envelopes for a more complete listing.
The collection was largely unarranged at the end of 2008 but is expected to be processed in the future. As a result, some file names/locations may change. Contact a reference archivist at the repository for assistance locating a specific file or item.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5933: Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union News files
National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees.; National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees. Local 1199 Drug & Hospital Union (New York, N.Y.); Bread and Roses Cultural Project.
5736582
- 1199 at Lincoln Center - tribute to Rosa Parks, 4/1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  12 photographs
- 1971 - 1199 Chorus (1) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  17 photographs
- 1971 - 1199 Chorus (2) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1199 Delegate Assembly - Jan. 1986-87 (1) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  22 photographs
- 1199 Delegate Assembly - Jan. 1986-87 (2) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  2 photographs
- 1199 Demonstration at Hahnemann - May 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  4 photographs
- 1199 Election 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  6 photographs
- April 1971 - 1199 goes to a wedding (Box 1, Folder 8)
  21 photographs
- 3/1971 - 1199 Kids Speak Out (Box 1, Folder 9)
  23 photographs
- 3/1971 - 1199 Kids Speak Out (Cont.) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  7 photographs
- 1199 Movie Photos (Box 1, Folder 11)
  25 photographs
- 1199 Movie Photos (cont.) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 1199 Movie Photos - Film Strips (Box 1, Folder 13)
  1 photograph
- 1199 Plaza (Box 1, Folder 14)
  19 photographs
- 1967 - 1199 Sends Newark Poor Kids to Camp (Box 1, Folder 15)
- 1967 - 1199 Sends Newark Poor Kids to Camp (cont.) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  8 photographs
- 1199 Training Program (Box 1, Folder 17)
- 1964 - 1199ers Visit Kennedy Grave in D.C. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  16 photographs
- 1199 w/UP Delegate Assembly - Sept. 18-19, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- 1199 - 25 Year Members Club - (Box 1, Folder 20)
  14 photographs
- Actors - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Actors-Norma Rae (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Actors-ABC Novel for Television-"Roots" (Box 2, Folder 2)
  26 photographs
- Actors-ABC Novel for Television-"Roots" (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Actors-Show (Box 2, Folder 4)
  15 photographs
- Actors-Shows and Group Cast Photos (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Actors-unidentified (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Actors-"The World of Winters" (Box 2, Folder 7)
- 1969 Adelphi - Jan.-Feb. Hospital - Leon Davis (Box 2, Folder 8)
  9 photographs
- 1969 Adelphi - Jan.-Feb. Hospital-Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 9)
  18 photographs
- Adelphi Hospital - Jan.-Feb. 1969 -- Police (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Adelphi Hospital - Strikers (1) (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Adelphi Hospital - Strikers (2) (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Affiliation (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Affiliation (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Affiliation (Box 2, Folder 15)
  11 photographs
- Agriculture (Box 2, Folder 16)
- A.I.D.S. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  4 photographs; 1 slide
- Albany March 1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Alda, Alan "Paper Lion" (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Alda, Alan "Paper Lion" (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Animals (Box 2, Folder 21)
- 25th Anniv. Banquet (1) (Box 2, Folder 22)
- 25th Anniv. Banquet (2) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  20 photographs
- Aug. 9, 1965 - annual 1199 Picnic (Box 3, Folder 1)
- 6th Annual Health Conf. - May 1976 (1) (Box 3, Folder 2)
- 6th Annual Health Conf. - May 1976 (2) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  24 photographs
- 6th Annual Health Conf. - May 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- 1979 Annual Health Care Conf. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Anti-Nuke demonstration - June 1982 (1) (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Anti-Nuke Demonstration - 6/12/1982 (2) (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Anti-Nuke Demonstration - 6/12/1982 (2) (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Anti-Nuke Demonstration - 6/12/1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Anti-Vietnam - Conference (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Anti-Vietnam - Conference (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Anti-Vietnam - Nat'l. Labor Leadership Assembly for peace (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Anti-Vietnam - Nat'l. Labor Leadership Assembly for Peace (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Anti-Vietnam - Rallies (Box 3, Folder 14)
  10 photographs
- Oct. 1971 - Anti-wage freeze demonstration (1) (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Oct. 1971 - Anti-wage freeze demonstration (1) (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Oct. 1971 - Anti-wage freeze demonstrations (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Oct. 1971 - Anti-wage freeze demonstration (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Anti-war demonstration - April 22, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- 1971 - Area dances (Box 3, Folder 20)
- 1971 Area dances (Box 3, Folder 21)
- 1971 - Area dances (3) (Box 3, Folder 22)
- 1971 - Area dances (4) (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Assemblies in action (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Assemblies in action (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Benefit and Fund - Patients (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Benefit and Fund - Patients (cont.) (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Astor's Visitors from Britain - 5/1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  13 photographs
- Awards - International Labor Press Association (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Ballot Hosp. Strike - Dec. 1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Baltimore Freedom Ride (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Baltimore Strike 12/1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Baltimore Strike, 12/1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Bart Lawson (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Benefit Fund - Children (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Benefit and Fund - Hospitals and Pharmacies (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Benefit and Fund - Meetings, Registration, ca. 1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Beth-Abraham Therapeutic - Community Project (Box 4, Folder 13)
- 1962 - Beth-El Brookdale Strike, Manhattan Eye & Ear (Box 4, Folder 14)
- 1962 - Beth-El Brookdale Strike, Manhattan Eye & Ear (2) (Box 4, Folder 15)
- 1962 - Beth-El Brookdale Strike - Manhattan Eye & Ear (3) (Box 4, Folder 16)
- 1962 - Beth-El Brookdale Strike - Manhattan Eye & Ear (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Beth Israel (Box 4, Folder 18)
  3 photographs
- Bill Myerson - Delegates Convention - Dec. 1983 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Blizzard of '78, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Blue Collar at work (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Brandywine Nursing Home Strike - April 27, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- 5/1974 - British Health Union Leaders visit (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Bronx (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Bronx (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Bronx (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Bronx (Box 5, Folder 9)
- 1199 News - Bronx Comm. Meetings (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Brookdale (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Brooklyn (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Brooklyn Area (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Brooklyn Area (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Brooklyn Jewish 1960 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- April 1970 - Brooklyn Jewish Hosp. Health Center (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Brooklyn Jewish - Fall 1979 (1) (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Brooklyn Jewish - Fall 1979 (2) (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Brooklyn Jewish - Fall 1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Brooklyn, Staten Island (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Brooklyn, Staten Island (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Brooklyn, Staten Island (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Bronx Community Action Project - 1968 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Buttons - Anti-Nuclear (Box 5, Folder 24)
- 1978 Calendar - Photos (Box 5, Folder 25)
- '78 Campaign, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Carey Endorsement 1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Chapter Patient Care Conf. - 1972 (Long Island Jewish) (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Chapter Patient Care Conf. 1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Chapter Patient Care Conf. - Montefiore (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Chapter Patient Care Conf. - Montefiore (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Chapter Patient Care Conference 1972 - Mt. Sinai (Box 6, Folder 6)
- 1969 Charleston - Drug and Hospital Employees Union (Box 6, Folder 7)
  5 photographs
- 1969 Charleston - Drug and Hospital Union Rally (Box 6, Folder 8)
- 1969 Charleston - Hospital Workers' Rally (Box 6, Folder 9)
- 1969 Charleston - Hospital Workers' Rally (Box 6, Folder 10)
- 1969 Charleston - Hospital Workers' Rally (Coretta King) (Box 6, Folder 11)
- 1969 Charleston - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 12)
- 1969 Charleston - Miscellaneous Rallies (1) (Box 6, Folder 13)
- 1969 Charleston - Miscellaneous Rallies (2) (Box 6, Folder 14)
- 1969 Charleston - People (1) (Box 6, Folder 15)
- 1969 Charleston - People (2) (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Charleston movie 1970 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- 1969 Charleston Strike March-July (1) (Box 6, Folder 18)
- 1969 Charleston Strike March-July (3) (Box 6, Folder 19)
- 1969 Charleston Strike March-July (3) (Box 6, Folder 20)
- 1969 Charleston Strike March-July (4) (Box 6, Folder 21)
- 1969 Charleston Strike March-July (Coretta King) (1) (Box 6, Folder 22)
- 1969 Charleston Strike March-July (Coretta King) (2) (Box 6, Folder 23)
- 1969 Charleston Strike March -July (J.P. Stevens) (Box 6, Folder 24)
- 1969 Charleston Strike March-July (UAW) (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Charleston June 11-14-Les Leon (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Charleston June 11-14-Les Leon (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Charleston Strike - David Fenton (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Charleston Strike - David Fenton (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Chillicothe, Ohio - Lost election 3/23/1983 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Chinatown Health Clinic - Oct. 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- X-Mas Kiddie Parties - Baltimore, NJ + NY (Box 7, Folder 7)
- 1962 Civil Rights Leasers rally in support (Box 7, Folder 8)
- 1962 Civil Rights Leaders rally in support (Box 7, Folder 9)
- 1962 Civil Rights Leaders rally in support (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Civil Service Rx Men (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Civil Service Rx Men (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Clerical Department (Box 7, Folder 13)
- 1968 Columbia U. org. drive (Box 7, Folder 14)
- 1968 Colombia U. org. drive - People (Box 8, Folder 1)
- 1968 Columbia U. org. drive - buildings and paraphernalia (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Community General Strike - Monticello, New York - December 1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Conference and Professional Committees (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Conference and Professional Committees (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Conference and Professional Committees (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Conference and Professional Committees (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Conference and professional Committees (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Conference and Professional Committees (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Connecticut Professionals 1/1979 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Connecticut Professionals - Jan. 1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Connecticut Nursing Home Strike - Dec. 1980 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Connecticut State Employees Vote 1199 (People) (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Connecticut State Employee Vote 1199 Rally (Box 8, Folder 14)
- 1976 Contract Campaign - ballots (Box 8, Folder 15)
- 1976 Contract Campaign - "Be Fair to Those Who Care" Rally (Box 8, Folder 16)
- 1976 Contract Campaign - Conferences (Box 8, Folder 17)
- 1976 Contract Campaign - Delegates Conference (Box 8, Folder 18)
- 1976 Contract Campaign - Democratic Convention, League Strike (Box 8, Folder 19)
- 1976 Contract Campaign - Cony Island Jewish Hospital (Box 9, Folder 1)
- 1976 Contract Campaign - Medical Center Strikes (Box 9, Folder 2)
- 1976 Contract Campaign - Miscellaneous Rallies and Strikes (Box 9, Folder 3)
- 1976 Contract Campaign - People (Box 9, Folder 4)
- 1976 Contract Campaign - Press Conference (Box 9, Folder 5)
- 1976 Contract Campaign - Rally Against Governor Carey (Box 9, Folder 6)
- 1976 Contract Campaign - Rally Against Governor Carey (Box 9, Folder 7)
- 1976 Contract Campaign (Box 9, Folder 8)
- 1976 Contract Campaign (Box 9, Folder 9)
- 1976 Contract Campaign (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 1976 Contract Campaign (Box 9, Folder 11)
- 1976 Contract Campaign (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Convention - Nat'l. Hospital Union - Dec. 10-13, 1975 -- Speakers (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Convention - Nat'l. Hospital Union - Dec. 10-13, 1975 -- Speakers (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Convention - Nat'l. Hospital Union - Dec. 10-13, 1975 - Attendees -- 2nd Constitutional (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Convention Nat'l. Hospital Union - Dec. 10-13, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Cook County - 3/1987 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Corey the Professor (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Coretta King at St. Luke's (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Creative Arts Therapists (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Crowd's and Demonstrations (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Crowded Hospital Waiting Rooms (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Cumberland Hospital Sit-in -- May 1968 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Day in the life of a Soda man (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Delegates Assemblies in Action (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Delegates Assemblies in Action (Box 10, Folder 9)
- 1966 Delegates Banquet (Box 10, Folder 10)
- 1968 Delegates Banquet + Instruction of Offices (Box 10, Folder 11)
- 1970 Delegates Banquet (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Delegates Convention - Dec. 1981 - Pictures of merger Ballot -- Attendees (1) (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Delegates Convention - Dec. 1981 - Pictures of Merger Ballot -- Attendees (2) (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Delegates Convention - Dec. 1981 -- Pictures of Merger Ballot -- Counting Ballots (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Delegates Convention - Dec. 1981 - Pictures of Merger Ballot -- Rallying (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Delegates Convention - Dec. 1981 - Pictures of Merger Ballot -- Speakers (1) (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Delegates Convention - Dec. 1981 - Pictures of Merger Ballot -- Speakers (2) (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Delegates Convention - Dec. 1981 - Pictures of Merger Ballot -- Work shops (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Delegates Convention - Dec. 1981 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Delegate Training (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Delegate Training (2) (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Delegate Training (RN) (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Demonstrations (Box 11, Folder 2)
- 1982 Demonstrations (Haiti, El Salvador) - 3/27 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Oct. 1984 - Demonstrations (Box 11, Folder 4)
- The Depression - Activities of visiting Nurses (Box 11, Folder 5)
- The Depression - films: Sacco + Vanzetti, Joe Hill, Norma Rae, Inheritance (Box 11, Folder 6)
- The Depression - Medieval Art (Box 11, Folder 7)
- The Depression - Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Diabetes Conf. -- Jan. 1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- 25 Year Dinner Dance - 4/22/1972 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- 1965 Discussion Forum Series -- March-June-Huntstein (Box 11, Folder 11)
- 1965 Discussion Forum Series -- March-June-Huntstein (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Dist. WV/KY/OH - Del. Assembly -- April 18-19, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Downtown (Box 11, Folder 14)